<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Karigusan</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="sample">\n\n
In the grand halls of Elsinore Castle, a shadowy specter appeared. It was the ghost of King Hamlet, the former ruler of Denmark, beckoning for his son, Prince Hamlet. The apparition revealed a haunting secret - his death was no accident but a murder most foul.
\n\n
Prince Hamlet, tormented by grief and betrayal, swore to avenge his fathers murder. He would feign madness, setting the stage for a chilling tale of deceit and treachery.
\n\n
As the courtiers of the castle watched, Hamlets eccentric behavior became a cause for concern. He questioned the motives of those around him, including his mother, Queen Gertrude, and her new husband, King Claudius, the murderer.
\n\n
Hamlets quest for justice unraveled a web of political intrigue and personal vendettas. He devised a plan to expose Claudius guilt through a play within a play, "The Mousetrap."
\n\n
The performance of "The Mousetrap" exposed Claudius guilt, sending shockwaves through the court. In the ensuing chaos, Hamlet confronted his mother, Gertrude, and unleashed a torrent of pent-up emotions.
\n\n
The tragic climax of "Hamlet" unfolded in the final act, where the fates of Hamlet, Ophelia, Laertes, and Claudius intertwined in a fatal dance of swords, poison, and madness.
\n\n
In the end, the castles halls were filled with death and despair. Hamlets quest for justice had come at a great cost, leaving only the silence of the dead.
\n\n
As the curtain fell on this tale of revenge and tragedy, one question lingered in the minds of those who witnessed it: "To be or not to be?" The legacy of "Hamlet" would endure as a timeless exploration of the human condition.
</string>

    <string name="brief">Bagasbas Beach, nestled in the scenic town of Daet in the Philippines, is a picturesque stretch of coastline renowned for its pristine sands and</string>


    <string name="cabana_desc">

        Looking for a beachfront escape thats all about casual fun vibes, refreshment, and affordability? Look no further! Our Cabana Bar and Beach Resort is about to undergo an exciting transformation to bring you a happy experience!
Whats in Store for You?
Refreshing Makeover: Were revamping our entire beach bar resort to create a more refreshing vibe!
Lively Fun: Get ready for a beachside party every day! From live music, and karaoke to fun-themed events, were all about creating a lively, fun vibe that keeps you smiling from sunrise to sunset.
Affordable Indulgence: At our Cabana Beach Bar, youll find affordable drinks and delicious bites. Sip on your favorite drinks without breaking the bank.
Beachside Bliss: We offer direct access to the beach, so youre just steps away from the waves. Unwind under the sun, take a dip, or simply soak in the breathtaking views. Tropical Airy Cabanas: Our cabanas are your private terrace. Lounge in your beach outfit and comfort and enjoy your stay.
Budget-Friendly: We believe that everyone deserves a taste of beauty and fun.
Dont miss out on our makeover and BIG PROMOS coming up!
Find us in Mangcamagong Boulevard, Basud Camarines, Norte
A great place to relax and unwind.
Discover Cabana Beach Bar and Resort on Mangcamagong Boulevard in front of calm, turquoise water and a beautiful sand beach view.
What to expect:
✓15-20mins away from Daet Centro
✓Available for day or overnight stay
✓Affordable rates
✓Excellent Wifi Connection
✓Good for friends and family
✓Available for tent pitching
✓High quality food
✓Accommodating Staffs
Amenities:
✓Beach Access
✓Beach Bar
✓Barbeque Area
✓Cabanas with View
✓Cabanas to Stay
✓Outdoor Shower
✓Free Wifi
Opens daily from:
8:00 am (Cabanas)
1:00 pm (Beach Bar)
Remember:
*Dispose your garbage properly.
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints.
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
*Enjoy and have a great Redventure!
EMAIL: cabanabeachbarresort@gmail.com
ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
4608, Bayan ng Basud, 4608 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/x2i2r2u4PrF1oHcKA
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/CABANABarAndBeachResort
 Resort tour: https://fb.watch/b_B8L9gmqt/
</string>
    
    <string name="zoilo_desc">
        POLICIES
1. Children and Persons with Disabilities shall always be attended by a companion.
2. The management will not in any way be responsible for any loss/or damage to the guests belongings including theft of pilferage.
3. Observe cleanliness at all times. Carry your garbage or pay 70 pesos per bag if left for management disposal.
4. Eating, drinking and smoking are strictly prohibited in the pool area.
5. Use of videoke is until 12am only.
6. Early check-in/latecheck-out other than the prescribed hours by the resort shall be in case to case basis and additional fees may apply.
7. Extra heads on the prescribed number of pax will be charged 200 pesos per head.
8. Downpayment per reservation is required. Three thousand pesos (P3,000) for exclusive reservation and one thousand pesos(P1,000) for room reservation.
Reservation fees are non-refundable but can be rebooked in proper coordination with the management.
9. Only two(2) pets are allowed but be sure that it is under the owners effective control.
10. Special set-up for events(eg. band, sound system) is subject to additional charges.
11. The guests will be held responsible for any loss or damage to the resort property caused by themselves, their guests or any persons for whom they are responsible.
The management reserved itself the right to add to alter/amend the above terms and conditions which are part of the Zoilo’s Seaside Private Resort policies.

ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
22JJ+5JP, Basud, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/tN55tQ7ktgPMuh6s9
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083832757806
 RESORT TOUR: https://fb.watch/b9ZsOyV2-i/


    </string>
    
    <string name="vieness_desc">
        What to expect:
✓ 15-20mins away from Daet Centro
✓ Front Beach view
✓ Nipa Hut with cottage (Up and down)
✓ Swimming Pool
✓ Barbeque Grill
✓ Mini Beach Volleyball Area
✓ Available for day or overnight stay
✓ Affordable rates
✓ Excellent Wifi Connection
✓ Good for friends and family
✓ Available for exclusive stay
✓ Available for tent pitching
For reservation and inquiries:
•Contact person: Rochie Pie
•Contact number: 09353732546
Remember:
*Dispose your garbage properly.
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints.
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
*Enjoy and have a great Redventure!

ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
Purok 2, Basud, 4608 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/6SkHR51VtWDdAj2Y6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083195207623
  RESORT TOUR: https://fb.watch/dE9lSowMq0/

    </string>

</resources>