<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Karigusan</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="sample">\n\n
In the grand halls of Elsinore Castle, a shadowy specter appeared. It was the ghost of King Hamlet, the former ruler of Denmark, beckoning for his son, Prince Hamlet. The apparition revealed a haunting secret - his death was no accident but a murder most foul.
\n\n
Prince Hamlet, tormented by grief and betrayal, swore to avenge his fathers murder. He would feign madness, setting the stage for a chilling tale of deceit and treachery.
\n\n
As the courtiers of the castle watched, Hamlets eccentric behavior became a cause for concern. He questioned the motives of those around him, including his mother, Queen Gertrude, and her new husband, King Claudius, the murderer.
\n\n
Hamlets quest for justice unraveled a web of political intrigue and personal vendettas. He devised a plan to expose Claudius guilt through a play within a play, "The Mousetrap."
\n\n
The performance of "The Mousetrap" exposed Claudius guilt, sending shockwaves through the court. In the ensuing chaos, Hamlet confronted his mother, Gertrude, and unleashed a torrent of pent-up emotions.
\n\n
The tragic climax of "Hamlet" unfolded in the final act, where the fates of Hamlet, Ophelia, Laertes, and Claudius intertwined in a fatal dance of swords, poison, and madness.
\n\n
In the end, the castles halls were filled with death and despair. Hamlets quest for justice had come at a great cost, leaving only the silence of the dead.
\n\n
As the curtain fell on this tale of revenge and tragedy, one question lingered in the minds of those who witnessed it: "To be or not to be?" The legacy of "Hamlet" would endure as a timeless exploration of the human condition.
</string>

    <string name="brief">Bagasbas Beach, nestled in the scenic town of Daet in the Philippines, is a picturesque stretch of coastline renowned for its pristine sands and</string>


    <string name="cabana_desc">

        Looking for a beachfront escape thats all about casual fun vibes, refreshment, and affordability? Look no further! Our Cabana Bar and Beach Resort is about to undergo an exciting transformation to bring you a happy experience!
Whats in Store for You?
Refreshing Makeover: Were revamping our entire beach bar resort to create a more refreshing vibe!
Lively Fun: Get ready for a beachside party every day! From live music, and karaoke to fun-themed events, were all about creating a lively, fun vibe that keeps you smiling from sunrise to sunset.
Affordable Indulgence: At our Cabana Beach Bar, youll find affordable drinks and delicious bites. Sip on your favorite drinks without breaking the bank.
Beachside Bliss: We offer direct access to the beach, so youre just steps away from the waves. Unwind under the sun, take a dip, or simply soak in the breathtaking views. Tropical Airy Cabanas: Our cabanas are your private terrace. Lounge in your beach outfit and comfort and enjoy your stay.
Budget-Friendly: We believe that everyone deserves a taste of beauty and fun.
Dont miss out on our makeover and BIG PROMOS coming up!
Find us in Mangcamagong Boulevard, Basud Camarines, Norte
A great place to relax and unwind.
Discover Cabana Beach Bar and Resort on Mangcamagong Boulevard in front of calm, turquoise water and a beautiful sand beach view.
What to expect:
✓15-20mins away from Daet Centro
✓Available for day or overnight stay
✓Affordable rates
✓Excellent Wifi Connection
✓Good for friends and family
✓Available for tent pitching
✓High quality food
✓Accommodating Staffs
Amenities:
✓Beach Access
✓Beach Bar
✓Barbeque Area
✓Cabanas with View
✓Cabanas to Stay
✓Outdoor Shower
✓Free Wifi
Opens daily from:
8:00 am (Cabanas)
1:00 pm (Beach Bar)
Remember:
*Dispose your garbage properly.
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints.
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
*Enjoy and have a great Redventure!
EMAIL: cabanabeachbarresort@gmail.com
ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
4608, Bayan ng Basud, 4608 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/x2i2r2u4PrF1oHcKA
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/CABANABarAndBeachResort
 Resort tour: https://fb.watch/b_B8L9gmqt/
</string>
    
    <string name="zoilo_desc">
        POLICIES
1. Children and Persons with Disabilities shall always be attended by a companion.
2. The management will not in any way be responsible for any loss/or damage to the guests belongings including theft of pilferage.
3. Observe cleanliness at all times. Carry your garbage or pay 70 pesos per bag if left for management disposal.
4. Eating, drinking and smoking are strictly prohibited in the pool area.
5. Use of videoke is until 12am only.
6. Early check-in/latecheck-out other than the prescribed hours by the resort shall be in case to case basis and additional fees may apply.
7. Extra heads on the prescribed number of pax will be charged 200 pesos per head.
8. Downpayment per reservation is required. Three thousand pesos (P3,000) for exclusive reservation and one thousand pesos(P1,000) for room reservation.
Reservation fees are non-refundable but can be rebooked in proper coordination with the management.
9. Only two(2) pets are allowed but be sure that it is under the owners effective control.
10. Special set-up for events(eg. band, sound system) is subject to additional charges.
11. The guests will be held responsible for any loss or damage to the resort property caused by themselves, their guests or any persons for whom they are responsible.
The management reserved itself the right to add to alter/amend the above terms and conditions which are part of the Zoilo’s Seaside Private Resort policies.

ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
22JJ+5JP, Basud, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/tN55tQ7ktgPMuh6s9
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083832757806
 RESORT TOUR: https://fb.watch/b9ZsOyV2-i/


    </string>
    
    <string name="vieness_desc">
        What to expect:
✓ 15-20mins away from Daet Centro
✓ Front Beach view
✓ Nipa Hut with cottage (Up and down)
✓ Swimming Pool
✓ Barbeque Grill
✓ Mini Beach Volleyball Area
✓ Available for day or overnight stay
✓ Affordable rates
✓ Excellent Wifi Connection
✓ Good for friends and family
✓ Available for exclusive stay
✓ Available for tent pitching
For reservation and inquiries:
•Contact person: Rochie Pie
•Contact number: 09353732546
Remember:
*Dispose your garbage properly.
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints.
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
*Enjoy and have a great Redventure!

ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
Purok 2, Basud, 4608 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/6SkHR51VtWDdAj2Y6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083195207623
  RESORT TOUR: https://fb.watch/dE9lSowMq0/

    </string>

    <string name="donmariano_desc">DESCRIPTION:\nSWIMMING POOL and BEACH\nEntrance:\nDAYTIME:(8 am-4 pm)-100\nOVERNIGHT:(5 pm-8 am)-120\nExcess-150\n23HOURS-20\n(infants-free)\nEXCLUSIVE PROMO RATES\nDaytime-12,500(40pax)\nOvernight-15,500(40pax)\n(4 pm-12nn)-18,500(40pax)\nRest House, Big House, 3-Cottages, 2-Cavanna\nFree: Videoke/all amenities\n7-table cement,2-kalesa table, griller, tent pitching\n23HOURS Promo\n9 AM-8 AM or 5 PM-4 PM\nREST House-6,500 (10 PAX)\nBIG House-9,500 (15 PAX)\nAvailable/Extra/Activities\nVideoke 700\nMineral water(blue gal) 50\nCooking (gasul) min of 100\nExtra bed(foam w/ bedsheet)-150\nSingle Mat-75\nBig Mat-100\nPillow-50\nBlanket-100\nTowel-100\nHammock-50\nElectric fan-100\nActivities:\nBoat Riding(wood)-100/hr (2 person)\nInflatable boat-150(1person)\nBeach VolleyBall-100/hr\nBeach InflatableBall-150/hour\nDETAILS: We have STORE inside the resort, PISO WIFI and GENERATOR in case of power interruption.\nAlong the road and 20-25 minutes travel from Daet\nCOTTAGE BAMBOO\n(10 person below)\nsahig na pweding tulugan\n700-daytime\n800-overnight\nCOTTAGE BAMBOO w/Attic\n(10 person below)\nsahig na pweding tulugan\n800-daytime\n1,000-night rate\nCAVANNA w/2 PAX\n(FREE ENTRANCE)\ninclusion:1-foam,mosquito net and electricfan\n800-daytime\n1,000-night rate\n1,500-23 hrs\nCAVANNA with DOUBLE BED\nw/4 PAX (FREE ENTRANCE)\ninclusion:2-Foam,2-electric fan and hammock\n1,600- daytime\n2,000-night rate\n2,800-23 hrs\nKalesa w/ umbrella\n(6 person below)\n500\nTable with umbrella\n(4 person below)\n300\nTent Renting- (can fit 2-3 person)\n400\n100-per tent set up\nFUNCTION HALL- 15 PAX (free)\n3,500-daytime only\n4 dining tables, 30 chairs, fixed chairs, wood sala set w/ 2-CR and Kitchen, terrace front view beach\nNOTE:\nBRING your kitchen utensils/cookware\nWe\'re accepting bookings w/50% down payment for confirmation\nCANCEL for any reason is not REFUNDABLE\nADRESS: Hanipaan Mercedes, Camarines Norte\n2322+6HV, Hinipaan, Mercedes, Camarines Norte\nGOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/HH9e4iz2YTT2smiD9\nFACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100077082007417</string>


    <string name="pambuhan_desc">
        Discover the ultimate escape at Pambuhan Glamping with our OFF SEASONS PROMO rate for cabanas.
Bring your loved ones and create unforgettable memories surrounded by beauty and serenity.
PAMBUHAN GLAMPING RESORT
EXPERIENCE UNIQUE | EXPERIENCE GLAMPING | EXPERIENCE NATURE
For real-time navigation, you can alternatively use GOOGLE MAPS or WAZE.
AMENITIES:
View Deck
Beach Access
Swimming pool
Bar
Function Hall
Balcony View
Cabanas to stay
Tables and Chairs
Toilet and Shower (outdoor)
Fully equipped kitchen
Bonfire area
Piso wifiVideoke
Pet friendly
Parking Area
For more inquiries kindly send us a message Pambuhan Glamping
ADDRESS: Purok 2 Brgy. Pambuhan Mercedes Camarines Norte
Purok 2, Brgy, Mercedes, 4601 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/qoYrgP7XcjwK9brX6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083041705050

    </string>
    
    <string name="palms_desc">
        all of our rooms are air-conditioned, the room rates are below:
CASA DE NIPA
Room 2 (maximum 6 persons): 5,400
Room 3 (maximum 2 persons): 2,300
Room 4 (maximum 4 persons): 3,600
Room 5 (maximum 4 persons): 3,600
Room 6 (maximum 6 persons): 5,400
CASITA
Victoria (2 bedrooms, maximum 8 persons): 11,200
Cecilia (4 bedrooms, maximum 16 persons): 22,400

entrance fees are below:

Day Rate (8am-5pm): 50.00 per person
Overnight Rate(6pm-7am): 60.00 per person
ADDRESS: Purok 4, Brgy. Cayucyucan, Mercedes, 4601 Camarines Norte
Purok 4, Brgy. Cayucyucan, Mercedes, 4601 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/tgZUkYe9psUWjFsq5
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/palmsfarmresort
EMAIL: palmsfarmresort@gmail.com

    </string>
    
    <string name="casanayon_desc">
        DESCRIPTION:
“A vacation helps to relieve stress and boredom, gives us a change of scenery, provides us with adventure, and helps to bring us closer to the people in our lives.” – E. S. Woods
Mobile Number: 09209296062

Casanayon Resort
ADDRESS:Purok 5, Bagong Silang 1, Labo, Camarines Norte Philippines
P-5 (Cruz Nayon, Bagong Silang - Capalonga Rd, Labo, Camarines Norte
EMAIL: casanayonresort@gmail.com 
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/ypQqbxW5jN57eXcS8 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/casanayonresort 

    </string>
    
    <string name="domeplace_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
What to expect:
✓5-7mins away from Labo Centro
✓Mt. Bagacay View
✓Available for day or overnight stay
✓Affordable rates
✓Excellent Wifi Connection
✓Good for friends and family
✓Accommodating Staffs
Amenities:
✓Swimming pool
✓Dome House
✓Family House
✓Container Room
✓Waterproof tent
✓Function Area
✓Parking area within the premises
✓Free WIFI
✓Board Games
✓Grilling Station
✓Cooking Utensils
For inquiries, contact them at 09420877841 or send a message to their official FB Page, DomePlace. 
Remember:
*Dispose of your garbage properly. 
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.  
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints. 
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
ADDRESS: Bulhao, Labo, Camarines Norte 
PSHIDA Village Bakiad/Bulhao , Labo, Philippines
5RFQ+7JW, Labo, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/ppUUPEe3U3oBi2mF9 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100088445234482 

    </string>
    
    <string name="maria_desc">
        DESCRIPTION:
Maria Fatima
THE MARIA FATIMA FARM RESORT WAS CONCEIVED AS A FAMILY BASED RESORT ROOTED ON THE CONCEPT OF PROVIDING A SIMPLE BUT MEANINGFUL RECREATIONAL FACILITY TO GUESTS AND VISITORS ALIKE WHILE AT THE SAME TIME OFFERING AMBIANCE OF VALUABLE INSIGHTS AND LOCAL AWARENESS ON THE IMPORTANCE OF A CLEAN, GREEN AND ECO-FRIENDLY ENVIRONMENT WHERE FAMILIES CAN RELAX AND ENJOY.
ENTRANCE:
Day Rate: (8AM-5PM)
Adult-
PhP 250.00
Kids -
PhP 150.00
Maria Fatima FARM RESOR
Night Rate: (5PM-10PM)
Adult-
PhP 280.00
Kids-
PhP 180.00
*Children three (3) feet below are free of charge.
POOL COTTAGES:
Cottages # 1,3,5,6, 8 and 10
PhP 700.00
(Small-good for 12 pax)
Cottages #2, 4, 7, and 9)- (Big-good for 20 pax)
PhP1,000.00
4 chairs and table-
Php 300.00
8 chairs and table.
PhP 400.00
OPEN PAVILION: (50 to 70 pax)
Day Rate-
PhP 10,000.00
Night Rate-
PhP 12,000.00
OTHER CHARGES:
Videoke
PhP 750.00
Electricity charge-
PhP 100.00
Electric kettle-
Php 50.00
Tent fee-
PhP 400.00
ADDRESS:Purok Bay Bautista, Labo, Camarines None 4604
Purok 2 Bgy, Bautista, Labo, 4604 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/J8oms9Nj4nAgcG6i6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100064116726231

    </string>
    
    <string name="garden_desc">
        DESCRIPTION:
Saan aabot Ang 3000 mo? 25 pax na ksama Mona family at barkada mo 
PRIVATE RESORT
OPEN FOR EARLY RESERVATION
For Inquiry and Reservation
Call 09095287749
Amenities
Pool unlimited
videoke
Speaker
Grill
Tables and Chairs
Parking space
NOTE: PLEASE BRING YOUR OWN UTENSILS
Secure 50% Downpayment to reserve your target date% legit 
No Downpayment , No Reservations
FIRST COME FIRST SERVE 
Mode of Payment
BPI bank,Gcash, or Any remittances center, 
CutOff time
8 am to 5 pm Daytime P3000
6 pm to 6 am Overnight P4000
22hrs 
8 am to 6 am
7 pm to 5pm
 AFFORDABLE PACKAGE FOR YOUR UPCOMING PARTIES
Birthday, Christening, Intimate Weddings, and any other parties!
28k lang kami na bahala sa Party flow kasi with party Host and Spinner 
As low as 28k good for 25 pax this is our inclusion 

VENUE
•PRIVATE RESORT
•Basic sound system
•Tables and Chairs
•Buffet Table
•3-4 hrs Venue
DECORATION
•Chosen theme
BUFFET CATERING(CONTROLLED)
•4 Main Dish
•Steamed Rice
•Softdrinks
•Complete basic utensils
•Waiters
•3hrs waiter service 
•Purified Water
•Dessert
Add ons:
•Pica2 Set up
•Dessert
•2tier cake
•Chair cover
•More decor
We also offer
•Food tray package
•Packed lunch
•Customize Cake

ADDRESS: AMIMAR SUBD LAG-ON DAET CAMARINES NORTE 
4W6M+QM2, San Vicente Rd, Daet, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAPS LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/PFq7Cumr2PBUQXbb9
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100087528226305 

    </string>
    
    <string name="pook_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
Searching for the ideal location to mark a special occasion? Look no further than Pook Mirasol Our private venue offers everything you need to make your birthday, reunion, or other event unforgettable. And with our beautiful and serene location, you can escape the hustle and bustle and enjoy a tranquil and relaxing atmosphere. So why wait? Book your event at Pook Mirasol today and experience the ultimate private venue for your next celebration!
You can easily reach us via (1) Borabod, passing Pabicol Abordo Elementary School or (2) via Mandulungan, take left turn before reaching bridge through Mercedes Road. 
You can also check us at Google Map.
AMENITIES
Swimming pool
Cabana (aircondtioned room with cr)
Bar
Open Kubo
Function Area
Tables and Chairs
Parking
Videoke
Kitchen
Piso Wifi
Pet friendly
Instagrammable spots

ADDRESS: Mandulungan, Brgy Gubat, Daet, Camarines Norte. 
Sitio Mandulungan Barangay Gubat, Daet, 4600 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/sMkc3sYsmZRtzujb8 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/Pookmirasol 
RESORT TOUR: https://web.facebook.com/watch/?v=589427822295164 

    </string>
    <string name="zams_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
Operation start 8:00am until 10:00pm.
Budget meal.
Cottage 200pesos
Entrance fee. Adult -100pesos
                          Kids-70pesos
Function hall-6,000 good for six hours with free videoke.
EMAIL: zamsgardenresort@yahoo.com
ADDRESS: Purok 1 barangay camambugan daet camarines norte.
4W3V+J6C, Daet, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/6eNTDZtKAiFo9Hss5
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/Zamsgardenresort

    </string>

    <string name="selfie_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
Looking for Staycation with your Barkada or Family? Youve come to the right place. Whether youre planning a relaxing and romantic short break, a sightseeing trip, or are in the area for business, youre sure of an enjoyable stay here at SELFIE BEACH RESORT
HERES OUR TREAT FOR YOU
You can Enjoy our JULY PROMO up to 40% OFF for all Rooms️
Hurry Up and book your stay with us we love turning good times into amazing memories, we are doing our best to improve all of our services and amenities for you!
So, what are you waiting for? Contact us now for bookings and reservations.
Please feel free to message us for inquiries:
☎️ | 0998-275-9564 • 0995-641-2659
REGULAR ROOM 3000 less 20% discount. inclusive for 2pax and free breakfast for 2,
300 for additional head with complete beddings and toilet amenities. 4pax room capacity.

FAMILY HOUSE 5000 less 20% discount. inclusive for 4 pax with free breakfast for 4.
300 for additional head  with complete beddings and toilet amenities. 8pax room capacity.

VIP ROOM 4000 less 20% discount. good for 2pax only. With free breakfast for 2. Beach front.
SELFIE BEACH RESORT RATES
ENTRANCE FEE
Day Tour (DT: 8:00 AM 6:00 PM): PHP 20.00
Night Tour (NT: 5:00 PM 4000 PM): PHP 30.00
Overnight (ON: 10:00 PM - 7:00 AM): PHP 40.00
You can rent your tent for only PHP 200 (bring your own mattress and pillows)
The Restaurant is open from 7:00 AM to 9:00 PM. Breakfast is served from 7:00 AM to 9:00 AM (for checked-in guests only).
You can rent also the mini event hall, good for 25 pax (free entrance fee for 19pax). Price ranges from PHP 2,000.00 PHP 3,000.00. Message them for queries and rates!
COTTAGES RATE:
BIG CABANA
PHP 500.00 for Day Tour PHP 800.00 for Night Tour PHP 1,000.00 for Overnight
SMALL CABANA
PHP 450.00 Day Tour PHP 600.00 Night Tour PHP 800.00 Overnight
UMBRELLA
PHP 350.00 Day Tour
PHP 500.00 Night Tour PHP 600.00 Overnight
EMAIL: selfieworldbeachandresortcorp@yahoo.com
ADDRESS: Brgy. Camagsaan, Capalonga, Camarines Norte
7FP9+6PQ, Camagsan, Purok 2, Capalonga, 4607 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/tAYv3LXpnVmPBhLp9
FACEBOOK PAGE:  https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100063934448128

    </string>
    
    <string name="greenland_desc">
        DESCRIPTION: 
 Day use of pool is P90 for adult and P60 for kids.
 They have cottages near the fishpond and some elevated. Price varies from P700-900. 
 They now have overnight accommodation for family and barkadas. Introducing their rustic and minimalistic interior design of glass windowed rooms with a great view of the ricefield and pool in the morning.
For reservation or advance booking
Please call us 02-7362422
When you can have a thrilling 
experience only here. Switch fear to fun! 
TRY our Newest  Greenland Giant Swing. 
Opening Promo rate : 50.00 php (Regular: 100.00)
 
ADDRESS:
Sitio Nico, Brgy. Dalnac, Paracale, Camarines Norte.
6QC5+GQG, Paracale, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK; https://maps.app.goo.gl/J6pQZ8MYJK6YKBQS9 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/bicolgreenlandresort 
RESORT TOUR: https://youtu.be/fUUJupHz59o 

    </string>
    <string name="candelaria_desc">
        DESCRIPTION:
 DESCRIPTION:
We have open cottages from PHP 1,000  (10-15 pax) and PHP 1,200 (15-20 pax) 8am-8pm Stay . Cabana Room RatesPHP. 3,500 Non ACPHP. 4,500 with ACMaximum 10 paxCheck in: 1PMCheck out: 12NN Entrance: Adult-40.00, Children 20.00 ( 10 y/o below) free toiletries(shampoo,body soap,toothbrush,toothpaste,tissue)
We strictly remind guests to follow health protocols. Safety is our priority.
Beach Resort in Paracale, Camarines Norte, Bicol, Philippines.
ADDRESS: Paracale, Camarines Norte
8Q3P+QF9, Paracale, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/5rp8tvRAiWnsNGks8 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/CandelariaBeachResort 
RESORT TOUR: https://youtu.be/HWn7wrydHBE 


    </string>
    
    <string name="gumaus_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
Take a quick gateway this holy week and enjoy your stay with us at the beautiful Gumaus Bay Resort
Our Facilities
Hotel Accommodation
Glamping
Restaurant
Bar
Gym
Trampoline (for kids)
Beach Front
Free Parking Area
Our Services
Island Hopping
Beach Party Organizer
DJ Party
Fire Dancing Show
Catering
Kayak Renting
Water Sports Renting

Book your stay at Gumaus Bay and make sure to make the most of your event!
ROOM RATE
(Breakfast Included)

Standard Room - P4,500 (3 pax)
Standard Room - P3,500 (2 pax)
Family Room  - P7,500 (6 pax)
Family Room- P5,500 (4 pax)
Family Room– P9,000 (8pax)

GLAMPING RATE

4500- Bell Tent for 4pax
3000- Pyramid Tent for 2pax
2500- Hunter Tent for 2pax
2500-Bell Tent for 2pax

|STANDARD CHECK IN AND CHECK OUT|
Check-In Time: 2:00pm
Check Out Time: 12:00nn
FEES
1. Day Tour Entrance - P100/Head  (6am to 6pm)
2. Night Tour Entrance- 150/head ( 4pm to 10pm)
3. Gazebo - P1000 (good for 6pax
4. Canopy- P1500 ( good for 15pax)
5. Food Corkage - P100/head
5. Grill usage - 200/day
6.. Acohol Corkage: 300 per bottle and 500 per case (beer)
7.Tent Pitching (bring your own tent) - 500/person
EMAIL: gumausbayresort2@gmail.com
ADDRESS: Purok 8 Brgy. Gumaus, Paracale, Camarines Norte
8P5M+GJ, Purok 8, Paracale, 4605 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/uyuwq27kuXQwHTKb7
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/GumausBayResort

    </string>

    <string name="mambulao_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
"Your great escape, a paradise awaits."

Indulge yourself in an infinity pool that overlooks the lush, green mountainside offers breathtaking views and sumptuous sunsets.

Located at Bagong Bayang Jose Panganiban Camarines Norte Established in 2019 Owned by Panganiban Family

Visit Mambulao pacific Resort, a perfect spot for a summer getaway surrounded by beautiful landscapes and modern rooms set up with completely equipped furniture.

Offering a relaxing ambiance, the best meals you NEED to try this season,  with stunning scenery, and Infinity Pool offers you the indulgence of truly private moments during your getaway.

The intimacy between the pools and the resorts beauty pervades the disarming charm and irresistible radiance of this place.

To all byaheros who want to stay overnight, Mambulao pacific Resort offers a comfortable double bed, a Smart tv, and a clean bathroom with a cold and hot shower. The exterior features an outdoor infinity pool, dining area, exceptional views of the sea, the sunset, and an Instagram-worthy spot.

The owner loves to travel, so the Panganiban family decided to have their own hotel and resort instead of going to distant places. The additional infinity pool offer events place for any occasion.

With an Excellent team, relational, and accommodating service staff, the resort also offers Good facilities, the best cuisine, and hot coffee.

Experience that glorious paradise, get all those satisfactions in an ideal resort with your friends and family for your escapade outside the city!

Mambulao pacific Resort
offers Hotel and Lodging
Function Hall and Catering Services
they have the best Restaurant in town and don’t miss out on their infinity
Pool
Amenities:
✓Unlimited Pool Access
✓Wireless Internet Connection
✓Air Conditioned Room
✓Hot and Cold Shower
✓Cable TV
✓Back-up Generator
PHONE: 0916 649 8443
ADDRESS: Bagong Bayan, Jose Panganiban, Camarines Norte
4606, Bayan ng Jose Panganiban, 4606 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/nfYTgyFCD1zNYZZU9
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/CABANABarAndBeachResort
 Resort tour: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ePYwFrUbEIE

    </string>
    <string name="noah_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
All day tour guests will have to pay entrance fee 80 php each.

- Overnight guests for cottage rooms and cabanas will have to pay entrance fee of 80 php each.
- PWDs, Seniors and Children below 5 years old are 50% off in entrance fee.
- Entrance fee includes ecological fee, use of facilities: parking, pool, toilet and bath, changing areas and sand area.
HOURS: 9AM-5PM ONLY 300 UMBRELLA (4 pas) 500 BLUE TENT (6) 1200 SMALL CARANA (10 pax) 400 COTTAGE (500 BIG CARANA (15 pas) 600 NEST (8.pax) 600 PERGOLA (10 pas) OVERNIGHT OPEN COTTAGE HOURS: 5 PM TO 8 AM Camo Tipt Bath Ideal for grows and sutdoor sizing 1500 COTTAGE ROOM 2000 SMALL CABANA 2800 BIG CABANA (10 pes) CLOSED ROOMS HOURS: 2 PM TO 11 AM All rooms have own to outdoor seating and arcon Includes entrance fee, towels coretries 2500 CABIN 4000 CABIN CASITA + O 3000 CABIN 24000 OVERNIGHT OPEN COTTAGES Ideal for Groups and Outdoor Sleeping Common Toilet and Bath CLUBNOAH eco resort CHECK IN: 6 PM CHECK OUT: 8 AM Entrance Fee: 80/head Breakfast: Add 100 php/head Extension per hour: 200/hour Additional foam: 400/foam Additonal person: 100/pax SMALL CABANA 2000 php for 6 pax only 3 Foam Beds 1 Electric Fan BIG CABANA 2800 php for 10 pax only 5 Foam Beds Two Level Cabana Separate Sleeping Area 2 Electric Fans COTTAGE ROOM 1500 php for 2 pax only 1 Double Bed 1 Electric Fan All guests will have to go under our health check, sign our rules and answer health declaration form upon entry. Management has the right to escort outside the premises those guests who are deemed unruly and loud.
EMAIL: clubnoahecoresort@gmail.com
ADDRESS: San Lorenzo Ruiz, Imelda, Philippines
2VVH+8V San Lorenzo Ruiz, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/P9FUroRiSrKSMpSX8
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/ClubNoahEcoResort

    </string>

    <string name="althea_desc">
        	Altheas Dreamland’s Resort
DESCRIPTION
INFINITY COUPLE ROOM
(2 person)
Room Amenities:
•Infinity Pool
•Hot and Cold Shower
•Fully Air-conditioned
•Garden Side Terrace
•Breakfast
•Entrance
₱4,500.00
VILLAS ROOM
(4 person)
Room Amenities:
•Hot and Cold Shower
• Fully Air-conditioned
•Garden Side Terrace
•Breakfast
•Entrance
₱7,000.00
PARK VIEW HOTEL ROOM
(8 person)
Room Amenities:
•Hot and Cold Shower
•Fully Air-conditioned
•Breakfast
•Entrance
₱12,500
Extra Person:
•Kids ₱500.00
•Adult ₱1,000.00
Cabana (2person)
- hot and cold shower
- fully air conditioned
- entrance
- breakfast
Umbrella (4-5 person) ₱500
Side Cottage (1-8 person) ₱1,000
Premium Cottage (10 person and up) ₱1,950
Daytime ₱180
Night time ₱230
EMAIL: altheasdresort11@gmail.com
ADDRESS: San Lorenzo Ruiz, Camarines Norte
2VRG+9F, Basud, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/arDjJwiZmELxtkji9
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100081282680204

    </string>

<string name="agri_desc">
    DESCRIPTION
Best way to wrap up this Cam Norte trip? A relaxing night at D’ Garden Agri Resort. Located about 10. minutes from Daet proper, this boutique resort offers just the right amount of privacy. The rooms are large, very homey feel. The pool offers slightly warm water temp perfect for relaxation. The staff are very friendly too. Its calming ambiance and nature themed interiors will give you that much needed relaxation for you and your loved ones to experience. For hotel inquiries and reservations, you may contact them at 0917-323 8128 or message their official FB page.
OTHER DETAILS: https://www.facebook.com/dgardenagriresort/posts/pfbid0mqkxPhCt214yN7SdGUkxCgHmEsyYQJiNrVaEgXS57c2Tw1R9QnH1HyH1ySdNQoZvl
EMAIL : dgardenagriresort@gmail.com
ADDRESS: Brgy. Calintaan, Talisay, Camarines Norte
4W8C+C9F, N.I.A Rd, Talisay, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LOCATION: https://maps.app.goo.gl/Ka1cAb8V1fpzK99A7
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://www.facebook.com/dgardenagriresort
RESORT TOUR: https://www.facebook.com/dgardenagriresort/videos/677198164257181/

</string>

    <string name="jars_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
LAP POOL

REGULAR SWIMMING:
Daytime: 8:00 am to 4:00 pm
Adult- (11y/o and above )Php 100.00/ head
Child- (2y/o to 10y/o) - Php 50.00/head

Night-Time: 6:00 pm to 12:00 am
Adult- (11y/o and above )Php 150.00/ head
Child- (2y/o to 10y/o) - Php 75.00/head

EXCLUSIVE SWIMMING POOL:
Daytime: 8:00 am to 4:00 pm
Good for 30 persons - Php 4,500
Additional Persons - Daytime Regular Rate

Night-Time: 6:00 pm to 12:00 am
Good for 30 persons - Php 5, 000
Additional Persons - Night-time Regular Rate

COTTAGE: P100.00
"For bookings and reservations visit us at Purok 10, Poblacion Sta.Elena, Camarines Norte or send us a call at (054) 8850763 or text us at mobile no. 09482452843"
ADDRESS: Purok 10, Poblacion Sta.Elena, Camarines Norte
59MR+RHW, Santa Elena, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/mtGmHAX7Lp95BpBdA
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://www.facebook.com/TheJars/
    </string>

    <string name="calaguas_desc">
DESCRIPTION
Private and exclusive resort located in Mahabang Buhangin, Vinzons, Camarines Norte. 1.5 - 2hr boat ride from the port.
Basic Package with tent accommodation:
2days/1 night = 3,500Php/pax
3days/2 nights = 4,500Php/pax
Inclusions:
Environmental fee
Boat Transfer
Port fee
Entrance
Full Board Meals
Activities:
Island hopping
Volleyball
Snorkeling
Trekking
Room Upgrade Options:
Fan rooms with use of common restroom.
Open Cabana = 3,500Php/night
Close Cabana = 5,500Php/night
A/C rooms with private restrooms:
Villa Double: good for 2 pax: 7,500Php/night
Villa Quad: good for 4 pax - 8,500Php/night
Family Villa: good for 8 pax max - 10,500Php/night
Dorm: good for 10 pax - 12,500Php/night
Executive Suite: good for 8 pax max 15,000Php/night
Presidential Suite: good for 8 pax max 15,000Php/night
*Extra mattress is additional fee
*No DIY
*We give preference to our guests that booked for a full package. All others will be on a waiting list.
*Down payment is required to book to be guaranteed services.
Package Offered
For 2Days1Night
P3,500/pax
Inclusions:
Full Board Meals
Boat Transfer
 Port Fee
 Environmental Fee
 Entrance
 Trekking
 Tent Accommodation
And heres our Room Accommodation Offered
AC Room with private CR and basic toiletries:
1-Presidential Room - P15,000/night (good for 4-6 person)
1-Executive Room - P 15,000/night (8-10 person)
2-Villa Quad - P8,500/night (good for 4-5 person)
2-Family Villa - P10,500/night (good for 6-8 person)
2-Villa Double - P7,500/night (good for 2-3 person)
2-Dorm Rooms - P 12,500/night (good for 7-10 person)
Fan Rooms/Cabanas and Basic Toiletries:
4-Close Cabana - P5,500/night (good for 2-3 persons)
6-Open Cabana - P3,500/night (4-6 persons)
4- Glamping- 4,500/night (up to 4-6 persons)
For inquiries and reservations, message our Facebook Page or dial
Smart: 09216348703/09394943165
Globe: 09560153255

ADDRESS: FWGQ+RQF, Mahabang Buhangin, Bayan ng Vinzons, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/z3c1gQLnKUqEownb6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://www.facebook.com/calaguasparadiseresort/

</string>

<string name="mananap_desc">
    DESCRIPTION
No Entrance Fee
No Registration Fee
LEAVE NO TRACE‼️kalat mo iuwi mo, Wala kang tagapulot‼️Take nothing but pictures Leave nothing but footprints Kill nothing but time
ADDRESS: 3R3G+HVX, Unnamed Road, San Vicente, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/qaTvWCtZNq2wtGndA
FACEBOOK PAGE : https://www.facebook.com/pages/Mananap-Resort/1428629444056536

</string>




</resources>