<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Karigusan</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="sample">\n\n
In the grand halls of Elsinore Castle, a shadowy specter appeared. It was the ghost of King Hamlet, the former ruler of Denmark, beckoning for his son, Prince Hamlet. The apparition revealed a haunting secret - his death was no accident but a murder most foul.
\n\n
Prince Hamlet, tormented by grief and betrayal, swore to avenge his fathers murder. He would feign madness, setting the stage for a chilling tale of deceit and treachery.
\n\n
As the courtiers of the castle watched, Hamlets eccentric behavior became a cause for concern. He questioned the motives of those around him, including his mother, Queen Gertrude, and her new husband, King Claudius, the murderer.
\n\n
Hamlets quest for justice unraveled a web of political intrigue and personal vendettas. He devised a plan to expose Claudius guilt through a play within a play, "The Mousetrap."
\n\n
The performance of "The Mousetrap" exposed Claudius guilt, sending shockwaves through the court. In the ensuing chaos, Hamlet confronted his mother, Gertrude, and unleashed a torrent of pent-up emotions.
\n\n
The tragic climax of "Hamlet" unfolded in the final act, where the fates of Hamlet, Ophelia, Laertes, and Claudius intertwined in a fatal dance of swords, poison, and madness.
\n\n
In the end, the castles halls were filled with death and despair. Hamlets quest for justice had come at a great cost, leaving only the silence of the dead.
\n\n
As the curtain fell on this tale of revenge and tragedy, one question lingered in the minds of those who witnessed it: "To be or not to be?" The legacy of "Hamlet" would endure as a timeless exploration of the human condition.
</string>

    <string name="brief">Bagasbas Beach, nestled in the scenic town of Daet in the Philippines, is a picturesque stretch of coastline renowned for its pristine sands and</string>


    <string name="cabana_desc">

        Looking for a beachfront escape thats all about casual fun vibes, refreshment, and affordability? Look no further! Our Cabana Bar and Beach Resort is about to undergo an exciting transformation to bring you a happy experience!
Whats in Store for You?
Refreshing Makeover: Were revamping our entire beach bar resort to create a more refreshing vibe!
Lively Fun: Get ready for a beachside party every day! From live music, and karaoke to fun-themed events, were all about creating a lively, fun vibe that keeps you smiling from sunrise to sunset.
Affordable Indulgence: At our Cabana Beach Bar, youll find affordable drinks and delicious bites. Sip on your favorite drinks without breaking the bank.
Beachside Bliss: We offer direct access to the beach, so youre just steps away from the waves. Unwind under the sun, take a dip, or simply soak in the breathtaking views. Tropical Airy Cabanas: Our cabanas are your private terrace. Lounge in your beach outfit and comfort and enjoy your stay.
Budget-Friendly: We believe that everyone deserves a taste of beauty and fun.
Dont miss out on our makeover and BIG PROMOS coming up!
Find us in Mangcamagong Boulevard, Basud Camarines, Norte
A great place to relax and unwind.
Discover Cabana Beach Bar and Resort on Mangcamagong Boulevard in front of calm, turquoise water and a beautiful sand beach view.
What to expect:
✓15-20mins away from Daet Centro
✓Available for day or overnight stay
✓Affordable rates
✓Excellent Wifi Connection
✓Good for friends and family
✓Available for tent pitching
✓High quality food
✓Accommodating Staffs
Amenities:
✓Beach Access
✓Beach Bar
✓Barbeque Area
✓Cabanas with View
✓Cabanas to Stay
✓Outdoor Shower
✓Free Wifi
Opens daily from:
8:00 am (Cabanas)
1:00 pm (Beach Bar)
Remember:
*Dispose your garbage properly.
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints.
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
*Enjoy and have a great Redventure!
EMAIL: cabanabeachbarresort@gmail.com
ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
4608, Bayan ng Basud, 4608 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/x2i2r2u4PrF1oHcKA
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/CABANABarAndBeachResort
 Resort tour: https://fb.watch/b_B8L9gmqt/
</string>
    
    <string name="zoilo_desc">
        POLICIES
1. Children and Persons with Disabilities shall always be attended by a companion.
2. The management will not in any way be responsible for any loss/or damage to the guests belongings including theft of pilferage.
3. Observe cleanliness at all times. Carry your garbage or pay 70 pesos per bag if left for management disposal.
4. Eating, drinking and smoking are strictly prohibited in the pool area.
5. Use of videoke is until 12am only.
6. Early check-in/latecheck-out other than the prescribed hours by the resort shall be in case to case basis and additional fees may apply.
7. Extra heads on the prescribed number of pax will be charged 200 pesos per head.
8. Downpayment per reservation is required. Three thousand pesos (P3,000) for exclusive reservation and one thousand pesos(P1,000) for room reservation.
Reservation fees are non-refundable but can be rebooked in proper coordination with the management.
9. Only two(2) pets are allowed but be sure that it is under the owners effective control.
10. Special set-up for events(eg. band, sound system) is subject to additional charges.
11. The guests will be held responsible for any loss or damage to the resort property caused by themselves, their guests or any persons for whom they are responsible.
The management reserved itself the right to add to alter/amend the above terms and conditions which are part of the Zoilo’s Seaside Private Resort policies.

ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
22JJ+5JP, Basud, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/tN55tQ7ktgPMuh6s9
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083832757806
 RESORT TOUR: https://fb.watch/b9ZsOyV2-i/


    </string>
    
    <string name="vieness_desc">
        What to expect:
✓ 15-20mins away from Daet Centro
✓ Front Beach view
✓ Nipa Hut with cottage (Up and down)
✓ Swimming Pool
✓ Barbeque Grill
✓ Mini Beach Volleyball Area
✓ Available for day or overnight stay
✓ Affordable rates
✓ Excellent Wifi Connection
✓ Good for friends and family
✓ Available for exclusive stay
✓ Available for tent pitching
For reservation and inquiries:
•Contact person: Rochie Pie
•Contact number: 09353732546
Remember:
*Dispose your garbage properly.
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints.
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
*Enjoy and have a great Redventure!

ADDRESS: Mangcamagong, Basud, Camarines Norte
Purok 2, Basud, 4608 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/6SkHR51VtWDdAj2Y6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083195207623
  RESORT TOUR: https://fb.watch/dE9lSowMq0/

    </string>

    <string name="donmariano_desc">DESCRIPTION:\nSWIMMING POOL and BEACH\nEntrance:\nDAYTIME:(8 am-4 pm)-100\nOVERNIGHT:(5 pm-8 am)-120\nExcess-150\n23HOURS-20\n(infants-free)\nEXCLUSIVE PROMO RATES\nDaytime-12,500(40pax)\nOvernight-15,500(40pax)\n(4 pm-12nn)-18,500(40pax)\nRest House, Big House, 3-Cottages, 2-Cavanna\nFree: Videoke/all amenities\n7-table cement,2-kalesa table, griller, tent pitching\n23HOURS Promo\n9 AM-8 AM or 5 PM-4 PM\nREST House-6,500 (10 PAX)\nBIG House-9,500 (15 PAX)\nAvailable/Extra/Activities\nVideoke 700\nMineral water(blue gal) 50\nCooking (gasul) min of 100\nExtra bed(foam w/ bedsheet)-150\nSingle Mat-75\nBig Mat-100\nPillow-50\nBlanket-100\nTowel-100\nHammock-50\nElectric fan-100\nActivities:\nBoat Riding(wood)-100/hr (2 person)\nInflatable boat-150(1person)\nBeach VolleyBall-100/hr\nBeach InflatableBall-150/hour\nDETAILS: We have STORE inside the resort, PISO WIFI and GENERATOR in case of power interruption.\nAlong the road and 20-25 minutes travel from Daet\nCOTTAGE BAMBOO\n(10 person below)\nsahig na pweding tulugan\n700-daytime\n800-overnight\nCOTTAGE BAMBOO w/Attic\n(10 person below)\nsahig na pweding tulugan\n800-daytime\n1,000-night rate\nCAVANNA w/2 PAX\n(FREE ENTRANCE)\ninclusion:1-foam,mosquito net and electricfan\n800-daytime\n1,000-night rate\n1,500-23 hrs\nCAVANNA with DOUBLE BED\nw/4 PAX (FREE ENTRANCE)\ninclusion:2-Foam,2-electric fan and hammock\n1,600- daytime\n2,000-night rate\n2,800-23 hrs\nKalesa w/ umbrella\n(6 person below)\n500\nTable with umbrella\n(4 person below)\n300\nTent Renting- (can fit 2-3 person)\n400\n100-per tent set up\nFUNCTION HALL- 15 PAX (free)\n3,500-daytime only\n4 dining tables, 30 chairs, fixed chairs, wood sala set w/ 2-CR and Kitchen, terrace front view beach\nNOTE:\nBRING your kitchen utensils/cookware\nWe\'re accepting bookings w/50% down payment for confirmation\nCANCEL for any reason is not REFUNDABLE\nADRESS: Hanipaan Mercedes, Camarines Norte\n2322+6HV, Hinipaan, Mercedes, Camarines Norte\nGOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/HH9e4iz2YTT2smiD9\nFACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100077082007417</string>


    <string name="pambuhan_desc">
        Discover the ultimate escape at Pambuhan Glamping with our OFF SEASONS PROMO rate for cabanas.
Bring your loved ones and create unforgettable memories surrounded by beauty and serenity.
PAMBUHAN GLAMPING RESORT
EXPERIENCE UNIQUE | EXPERIENCE GLAMPING | EXPERIENCE NATURE
For real-time navigation, you can alternatively use GOOGLE MAPS or WAZE.
AMENITIES:
View Deck
Beach Access
Swimming pool
Bar
Function Hall
Balcony View
Cabanas to stay
Tables and Chairs
Toilet and Shower (outdoor)
Fully equipped kitchen
Bonfire area
Piso wifiVideoke
Pet friendly
Parking Area
For more inquiries kindly send us a message Pambuhan Glamping
ADDRESS: Purok 2 Brgy. Pambuhan Mercedes Camarines Norte
Purok 2, Brgy, Mercedes, 4601 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/qoYrgP7XcjwK9brX6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100083041705050

    </string>
    
    <string name="palms_desc">
        all of our rooms are air-conditioned, the room rates are below:
CASA DE NIPA
Room 2 (maximum 6 persons): 5,400
Room 3 (maximum 2 persons): 2,300
Room 4 (maximum 4 persons): 3,600
Room 5 (maximum 4 persons): 3,600
Room 6 (maximum 6 persons): 5,400
CASITA
Victoria (2 bedrooms, maximum 8 persons): 11,200
Cecilia (4 bedrooms, maximum 16 persons): 22,400

entrance fees are below:

Day Rate (8am-5pm): 50.00 per person
Overnight Rate(6pm-7am): 60.00 per person
ADDRESS: Purok 4, Brgy. Cayucyucan, Mercedes, 4601 Camarines Norte
Purok 4, Brgy. Cayucyucan, Mercedes, 4601 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/tgZUkYe9psUWjFsq5
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/palmsfarmresort
EMAIL: palmsfarmresort@gmail.com

    </string>
    
    <string name="casanayon_desc">
        DESCRIPTION:
“A vacation helps to relieve stress and boredom, gives us a change of scenery, provides us with adventure, and helps to bring us closer to the people in our lives.” – E. S. Woods
Mobile Number: 09209296062

Casanayon Resort
ADDRESS:Purok 5, Bagong Silang 1, Labo, Camarines Norte Philippines
P-5 (Cruz Nayon, Bagong Silang - Capalonga Rd, Labo, Camarines Norte
EMAIL: casanayonresort@gmail.com 
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/ypQqbxW5jN57eXcS8 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/casanayonresort 

    </string>
    
    <string name="domeplace_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
What to expect:
✓5-7mins away from Labo Centro
✓Mt. Bagacay View
✓Available for day or overnight stay
✓Affordable rates
✓Excellent Wifi Connection
✓Good for friends and family
✓Accommodating Staffs
Amenities:
✓Swimming pool
✓Dome House
✓Family House
✓Container Room
✓Waterproof tent
✓Function Area
✓Parking area within the premises
✓Free WIFI
✓Board Games
✓Grilling Station
✓Cooking Utensils
For inquiries, contact them at 09420877841 or send a message to their official FB Page, DomePlace. 
Remember:
*Dispose of your garbage properly. 
*Always remember to be a responsible tourist.  
*Take nothing but pictures.
*Leave nothing but footprints. 
*Observe proper health and safety protocols.
ADDRESS: Bulhao, Labo, Camarines Norte 
PSHIDA Village Bakiad/Bulhao , Labo, Philippines
5RFQ+7JW, Labo, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/ppUUPEe3U3oBi2mF9 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100088445234482 

    </string>
    
    <string name="maria_desc">
        DESCRIPTION:
Maria Fatima
THE MARIA FATIMA FARM RESORT WAS CONCEIVED AS A FAMILY BASED RESORT ROOTED ON THE CONCEPT OF PROVIDING A SIMPLE BUT MEANINGFUL RECREATIONAL FACILITY TO GUESTS AND VISITORS ALIKE WHILE AT THE SAME TIME OFFERING AMBIANCE OF VALUABLE INSIGHTS AND LOCAL AWARENESS ON THE IMPORTANCE OF A CLEAN, GREEN AND ECO-FRIENDLY ENVIRONMENT WHERE FAMILIES CAN RELAX AND ENJOY.
ENTRANCE:
Day Rate: (8AM-5PM)
Adult-
PhP 250.00
Kids -
PhP 150.00
Maria Fatima FARM RESOR
Night Rate: (5PM-10PM)
Adult-
PhP 280.00
Kids-
PhP 180.00
*Children three (3) feet below are free of charge.
POOL COTTAGES:
Cottages # 1,3,5,6, 8 and 10
PhP 700.00
(Small-good for 12 pax)
Cottages #2, 4, 7, and 9)- (Big-good for 20 pax)
PhP1,000.00
4 chairs and table-
Php 300.00
8 chairs and table.
PhP 400.00
OPEN PAVILION: (50 to 70 pax)
Day Rate-
PhP 10,000.00
Night Rate-
PhP 12,000.00
OTHER CHARGES:
Videoke
PhP 750.00
Electricity charge-
PhP 100.00
Electric kettle-
Php 50.00
Tent fee-
PhP 400.00
ADDRESS:Purok Bay Bautista, Labo, Camarines None 4604
Purok 2 Bgy, Bautista, Labo, 4604 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/J8oms9Nj4nAgcG6i6
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100064116726231

    </string>
    
    <string name="garden_desc">
        DESCRIPTION:
Saan aabot Ang 3000 mo? 25 pax na ksama Mona family at barkada mo 
PRIVATE RESORT
OPEN FOR EARLY RESERVATION
For Inquiry and Reservation
Call 09095287749
Amenities
Pool unlimited
videoke
Speaker
Grill
Tables and Chairs
Parking space
NOTE: PLEASE BRING YOUR OWN UTENSILS
Secure 50% Downpayment to reserve your target date% legit 
No Downpayment , No Reservations
FIRST COME FIRST SERVE 
Mode of Payment
BPI bank,Gcash, or Any remittances center, 
CutOff time
8 am to 5 pm Daytime P3000
6 pm to 6 am Overnight P4000
22hrs 
8 am to 6 am
7 pm to 5pm
 AFFORDABLE PACKAGE FOR YOUR UPCOMING PARTIES
Birthday, Christening, Intimate Weddings, and any other parties!
28k lang kami na bahala sa Party flow kasi with party Host and Spinner 
As low as 28k good for 25 pax this is our inclusion 

VENUE
•PRIVATE RESORT
•Basic sound system
•Tables and Chairs
•Buffet Table
•3-4 hrs Venue
DECORATION
•Chosen theme
BUFFET CATERING(CONTROLLED)
•4 Main Dish
•Steamed Rice
•Softdrinks
•Complete basic utensils
•Waiters
•3hrs waiter service 
•Purified Water
•Dessert
Add ons:
•Pica2 Set up
•Dessert
•2tier cake
•Chair cover
•More decor
We also offer
•Food tray package
•Packed lunch
•Customize Cake

ADDRESS: AMIMAR SUBD LAG-ON DAET CAMARINES NORTE 
4W6M+QM2, San Vicente Rd, Daet, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAPS LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/PFq7Cumr2PBUQXbb9
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100087528226305 

    </string>
    
    <string name="pook_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
Searching for the ideal location to mark a special occasion? Look no further than Pook Mirasol Our private venue offers everything you need to make your birthday, reunion, or other event unforgettable. And with our beautiful and serene location, you can escape the hustle and bustle and enjoy a tranquil and relaxing atmosphere. So why wait? Book your event at Pook Mirasol today and experience the ultimate private venue for your next celebration!
You can easily reach us via (1) Borabod, passing Pabicol Abordo Elementary School or (2) via Mandulungan, take left turn before reaching bridge through Mercedes Road. 
You can also check us at Google Map.
AMENITIES
Swimming pool
Cabana (aircondtioned room with cr)
Bar
Open Kubo
Function Area
Tables and Chairs
Parking
Videoke
Kitchen
Piso Wifi
Pet friendly
Instagrammable spots

ADDRESS: Mandulungan, Brgy Gubat, Daet, Camarines Norte. 
Sitio Mandulungan Barangay Gubat, Daet, 4600 Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/sMkc3sYsmZRtzujb8 
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/Pookmirasol 
RESORT TOUR: https://web.facebook.com/watch/?v=589427822295164 

    </string>
    <string name="zams_desc">
        DESCRIPTION
Operation start 8:00am until 10:00pm.
Budget meal.
Cottage 200pesos
Entrance fee. Adult -100pesos
                          Kids-70pesos
Function hall-6,000 good for six hours with free videoke.
EMAIL: zamsgardenresort@yahoo.com
ADDRESS: Purok 1 barangay camambugan daet camarines norte.
4W3V+J6C, Daet, Camarines Norte
GOOGLE MAP LINK: https://maps.app.goo.gl/6eNTDZtKAiFo9Hss5
FACEBOOK PAGE: https://web.facebook.com/Zamsgardenresort

    </string>
</resources>